export const questions = [
  [
    { question: "Question 1: 5 + 3 = ?", answer: 8 },
    { question: "Question 2: 10 - 6 = ?", answer: 4 },
    { question: "Question 3: 6 * 2 = ?", answer: 12 },
    { question: "Question 4: 8 / 2 = ?", answer: 4 },
    { question: "Question 5: 9 + 1 = ?", answer: 10 },
    { question: "Question 6: 7 * 3 = ?", answer: 21 },
    { question: "Question 7: 12 - 4 = ?", answer: 8 },
    { question: "Question 8: 15 / 5 = ?", answer: 3 },
    { question: "Question 9: 3 * 5 = ?", answer: 15 },
    { question: "Question 10: 10 + 7 = ?", answer: 17 },
  ],
  [
    { question: "Question 1: 15 + 5 = ?", answer: 20 },
    { question: "Question 2: 20 - 8 = ?", answer: 12 },
    { question: "Question 3: 6 * 5 = ?", answer: 30 },
    { question: "Question 4: 40 / 8 = ?", answer: 5 },
    { question: "Question 5: 9 + 6 = ?", answer: 15 },
    { question: "Question 6: 24 / 4 = ?", answer: 6 },
    { question: "Question 7: 12 + 14 = ?", answer: 26 },
    { question: "Question 8: 30 - 10 = ?", answer: 20 },
    { question: "Question 9: 50 / 2 = ?", answer: 25 },
    { question: "Question 10: 18 + 2 = ?", answer: 20 },
  ],
  [
    { question: "Question 1: 25 + 10 = ?", answer: 35 },
    { question: "Question 2: 100 - 25 = ?", answer: 75 },
    { question: "Question 3: 12 * 3 = ?", answer: 36 },
    { question: "Question 4: 60 / 3 = ?", answer: 20 },
    { question: "Question 5: 90 + 10 = ?", answer: 100 },
    { question: "Question 6: 72 / 9 = ?", answer: 8 },
    { question: "Question 7: 35 * 2 = ?", answer: 70 },
    { question: "Question 8: 45 + 25 = ?", answer: 70 },
    { question: "Question 9: 50 - 30 = ?", answer: 20 },
    { question: "Question 10: 10 * 10 = ?", answer: 100 },
  ],
];